{
    "categories": [],
    "description": " Guess these religion-themed answers!",
    "difficulty": -1,
    "questions": [{
        "answer": "Eve",
        "category": "Religion A to Z",
        "question": "First woman"
    }, {
        "answer": "David",
        "category": "Religion A to Z",
        "question": "Slew Goliath"
    }, {
        "answer": "Jesus",
        "category": "Religion A to Z",
        "question": "The Christian Messiah"
    }, {
        "answer": "Noah",
        "category": "Religion A to Z",
        "question": "Famous ark builder & flood survivor"
    }, {
        "answer": "Francis",
        "category": "Religion A to Z",
        "question": "Pope following Benedict XVI"
    }, {
        "answer": "Qur'an",
        "category": "Religion A to Z",
        "question": "Holy book of Islam"
    }, {
        "answer": "Buddha",
        "category": "Religion A to Z",
        "question": "SiddhƒÅrtha Gautama"
    }, {
        "answer": "Isaac",
        "category": "Religion A to Z",
        "question": "Second son of Abraham"
    }, {
        "answer": "Yoga",
        "category": "Religion A to Z",
        "question": "Hindu meditation with poses"
    }, {
        "answer": "Protestants",
        "category": "Religion A to Z",
        "question": "Christians who followed Luther"
    }, {
        "answer": "Rastafarianism",
        "category": "Religion A to Z",
        "question": "Jamaican born ideology"
    }, {
        "answer": "Torah",
        "category": "Religion A to Z",
        "question": "First five books of the Jewish Bible"
    }, {
        "answer": "Lot",
        "category": "Religion A to Z",
        "question": "His wife became a pillar of salt"
    }, {
        "answer": "Vishnu",
        "category": "Religion A to Z",
        "question": "Blue four-armed Hindu God"
    }, {
        "answer": "Aaron",
        "category": "Religion A to Z",
        "question": "Older brother of Moses"
    }, {
        "answer": "Canaan",
        "category": "Religion A to Z",
        "question": "The land God promised the Israelites"
    }, {
        "answer": "Hajj",
        "category": "Religion A to Z",
        "question": "Muslim pilgrimage"
    }, {
        "answer": "Shinto",
        "category": "Religion A to Z",
        "question": "Indigenous religion of Japan"
    }, {
        "answer": "Zion",
        "category": "Religion A to Z",
        "question": "The Holy Land - synonymous with Jerusalem"
    }, {
        "answer": "Wicca",
        "category": "Religion A to Z",
        "question": "Modern pagan religion symbolized by a pentagram"
    }, {
        "answer": "Gideons",
        "category": "Religion A to Z",
        "question": "Hotel room Bible distributor"
    }, {
        "answer": "Minaret",
        "category": "Religion A to Z",
        "question": "Mosque tower from which the call to prayer is made"
    }, {
        "answer": "Kaaba",
        "category": "Religion A to Z",
        "question": "Cube-shaped building in Mecca; Islam's most holy site"
    }, {
        "answer": "Ur",
        "category": "Religion A to Z",
        "question": "Birthplace of Abraham"
    }, {
        "answer": "Obadiah",
        "category": "Religion A to Z",
        "question": "Shortest book of the Hebrew Bible"
    }, {
        "answer": "Xian",
        "category": "Religion A to Z",
        "question": "Taoist term for an enlightened person"
    }],
    "quizLength": 26,
    "title": "Religion A to Z",
    "url": "http://www.jetpunk.com/user-quizzes/33027/religion-a-to-z"
}